grave me grave me Spring
tumba me tumba Spring
[Music]
[Música]
I really don't understand but it was
yo de verdad no lo entiendo pero fue
Beijing to see friends yes yes it's true that
Beijing a ver amigos sí sí que es verdad
people with faith think Beijing that the
que pensa la gente con fe Beijing que la
last arrow is from Beijing but to
última flecha es de Beijing pero
use that is to be a
usarse en eso es de ser un ser
pathetic being who has simply shot an
lamentable que simplemente ha tirado una
accidental arrow and to load that
flecha accidental y cargarle a esa
person with the weight of a death that is to
persona el peso de una muerte eso es de
be a pathetic and sad being I
ser un ser lamentable y triste yo
would have died Likewise clinging to
hubiera muerto Igualmente agarrarse a
that or you are two years old or or I don't know what's
eso o tienes dos años o o no sé qué te
wrong with your brain the truth here a
pasa en el cerebro la verdad aquí un
little yes to this day it is taken very badly
poco sí al día de hoy se la toma muy mal
eh sincerely guys really is a
eh sinceramente chicos de verdad es un
[ __ ] game I mean and I'm fighting
puñetero juego o sea y estoy peleando
for rich people I mean it's that touch them I
por gente rica O sea es que tócate los
lame or be so stupid You're going to be a
cojo o sea tan tontos Vais a ser un
moment I cried you piece of
momento he llorado yo trozo de mugre
infected filth at what moment if on the contrary it's
infecto en qué momento si al contrario
that what I said if this is extreme and
es que lo que dije si esto es extremo y
period I mean it's that no no
punto o sea es que no no